Publishable API Key:	sb_publishable_TpZmhKyB9Ybstn9rmCjGqQ_SJgIqPeo



Secret API Key:		sb_secret_sQsjzrPJeYpUpL6bgjwm1w_NXtXdqj6


NOTE: Keep in mind that I have enabled automatic RLS
MCP SETUP


1. Configure MCP
Set up your MCP client.
Details:
Add this configuration to ~/.gemini/antigravity/mcp_config.json:
After saving the config, restart Antigravity. It will prompt you to complete the OAuth flow to authenticate with Supabase.
To edit the config from within Antigravity, click the ···menu at the top of the Agent pane > MCP Servers > Manage MCP Servers > View raw config. From the Manage MCP Servers page you can also Refresh server configs and enable/disable servers.
If you run into authentication issues, open the command palette and run Authentication: Remove Dynamic Authentication Providers to clear cached OAuth credentials and re-authenticate.
Need help?View Antigravity docs
Code:
File: Code
```
1{
2  "mcpServers": {
3    "supabase": {
4      "serverUrl": "https://mcp.supabase.com/mcp?project_ref=ablvrbnbsdqshrorhmjf"
5    }
6  }
7}
```

2. Install Agent Skills (Optional)
Agent Skills give AI coding tools ready-made instructions, scripts, and resources for working with Supabase more accurately and efficiently.
Details:
npx skills add supabase/agent-skills
Code:
File: Code
```
npx skills add supabase/agent-skills
```



DIRECT CONNECTION STRING


1. Connection string
Copy the connection details for your database.
Details:
Not IPv4 compatibleUse Session Pooler if on a IPv4 network or purchase IPv4 add-onIPv4 add-onPooler settings
host:db.ablvrbnbsdqshrorhmjf.supabase.co
port:5432
database:postgres
user:postgres
Code:
File: Code
```
postgresql://postgres:[YOUR-PASSWORD]@db.ablvrbnbsdqshrorhmjf.supabase.co:5432/postgres
```

2. Install Agent Skills (Optional)
Agent Skills give AI coding tools ready-made instructions, scripts, and resources for working with Supabase more accurately and efficiently.
Details:
npx skills add supabase/agent-skills
Code:
File: Code
```
npx skills add supabase/agent-skills
```